Anthony Garonski

Customer Support Associate- Plumbing/Electrical

Philadelphia, PA - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Anthony-Garonski/445cb6045629a2a6

A position In-House or Field Service for a quality oriented company.

Highlights: * Over 20 years of progressive experience and responsibility with documented success in the areas of computer hardware at various organizational levels.

Related

WORK EXPERIENCE

Customer Support Associate- Plumbing/Electrical

LOWE'S - Plant City, FL - June 2005 to April 2011

I provide excellent customer support helping customers solve their plumbing and electrical problems in a cost effective manner.

Perform monthly price audit and cycle counts.

Put up and downstock product to shelves.

Make price changes and labels as needed.

f

Supervisor Hardware Dept

Micros of Central Florida - Tampa, FL - February 2003 to February 2005

- * Supervised technical support team of 5 dispatching them to various locations for repair/replacement of hardware.
- * Assigned in-house projects to complete.
- * Handled customer support hot line and repaired system boards, printers etc.
- * Also did Inventory control as well as coordinating customer installs.

Computer Technician

Micros P.O.S - Trevose, PA - June 2000 to January 2003

- * Repaired printers, circuit boards, and other equipment.
- * Handled service calls from customers, dispatched technicians.
- * Set up systems to customer specifications and did inventory control.

Technician Hardware Help Desk

SASI Inc - Bristol, PA - July 1994 to January 2000

- * Handled calls from customers and technicians across the US and Canada, troubleshooting questions on P.O.S., Dos, and Windows based systems.
- * Dispatched technicians to sites.

Field Engineer Communications

Halifax Inc - Warminster, PA - May 1993 to May 1994

- * Removed and relocated all Naval Base Communications equipment and cabling. This included CATV, ETHERNET, and FIBER-OPTICS.
- * Installed Network Cards, T-Boxes, and software.

Supervisor Corporate Support

Intelligent Electronics - Exton, PA - April 1986 to October 1992

- * Installed, upgraded, and, repaired all corporate systems (over200)
- * Set up their Token-Ring network and Inventory database.
- * Held positions starting as a field service technician, in-house technician/warranty claims specialist, and technical support advisor.
- * Set up technical hotline and pre-configured systems to customer specifications. Also handled warranty claims.

EDUCATION

Associates Electronic Engineering in Computers Electronics Etc.

Rets Electronics School - Broomall, PA January 1983 to January 1985